Storrs Agricultural Experiment Station Records 1972.0001
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Correspondence, 1897-1920
  - Brandon, Melvin, 1910-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:29 (Box-folder 2:29, Box 2, Folder 29 [39153019697418])
  - Brazil, 1904-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:30 (Box-folder 2:30, Box 2, Folder 30 [39153019697426])
  - Bree - Brew, 1904-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:31 (Box-folder 2:31, Box 2, Folder 31 [39153019697434])
  - Brentano's, 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:32 (Box-folder 2:32, Box 2, Folder 32 [39153019697442])
  - Brewer, N.H., 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:33 (Box-folder 2:33, Box 2, Folder 33 [39153019697459])
  - Brewer, William H - Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, undated; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:34 (Box-folder 2:34, Box 2, Folder 34 [39153019697467])
  - Bria - Brit, 1904-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:35 (Box-folder 2:35, Box 2, Folder 35 [39153019697475])
  - Bridge, John L., 1895-1897; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:36 (Box-folder 2:36, Box 2, Folder 36 [39153019697483])
  - Briggs, K. H., 1910-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:37 (Box 2, Folder 37 [39153019697491], Box-folder 2:37)
  - Bristol, Ralph, 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:38 (Box-folder 2:38, Box 2, Folder 38 [39153019697509])
  - Broa - Brou, 1905-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:39 (Box-folder 2:39, Box 2, Folder 39 [39153019697517])
  - Brown - Browne, 1914-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:40 (Box-folder 2:40, Box 2, Folder 40 [39153019697525])
  - Brown - Howland Company, Inc., 1908-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:41 (Box 2, Folder 41 [39153019697533], Box-folder 2:41)
  - Brown Brothers, 1905-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:42 (Box 2, Folder 42 [39153019697541], Box-folder 2:42)
  - Brown, E. A., 1916-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:43 (Box-folder 2:43, Box 2, Folder 43 [39153019697558])
  - Brown, J. Stanford, 1911-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:44 (Box-folder 2:44, Box 1, Folder 44 [39153019697566])
  - Brown, James F. (Col.), 1897-1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:45 (Box-folder 2:45, Box 2, Folder 45 [39153019697574])
  - Brown, John (Mansfield Creamery), 1894-1896; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:46 (Box-folder 2:46, Box 2, Folder 46 [39153019697582])
  - Brown,Thomas L., 1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:47 (Box-folder 2:47, Box 2, Folder 47 [39153019697590])
  - Bru - Bry, 1902-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:48 (Box-folder 2:48, Box 2, Folder 48 [39153019697608])
  - Brundage, A. J., Extension Service, 1916-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:49 (Box 2, Folder 49 [39153019697616], Box-folder 2:49)
  - Buc - Bun, 1903-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:50 (Box-folder 2:50, Box 1, Folder 50 [39153019697624])
  - Buddington, O. G., 1905-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:51 (Box-folder 2:51, Box 2, Folder 51 [39153019697632])
  - Buffalo Fertilizer Company, 1905-1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:52 (Box-folder 2:52, Box 2, Folder 52 [39153019697640])
  - Bulgaria, 1911-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:53 (Box-folder 2:53, Box 2, Folder 53 [39153019697657])
  - Bulletin Company, 1905-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:54 (Box-folder 2:54, Box 2, Folder 54 [39153019697665])
  - Bur - By, 1903-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:55 (Box-folder 2:55, Box 2, Folder 55 [39153019697673])
  - Burr, Clarence, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:56 (Box-folder 2:56, Box 2, Folder 56 [39153019697681])
  - Burr, Louis St. Clair, 1909-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:57 (Box 2, Folder 57 [39153019697699], Box-folder 2:57)
  - Burt, Fred M., 1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:58 (Box 2, Folder 58 [39153019697707], Box-folder 2:58)
  - Bushell, H. L., 1909-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:59 (Box-folder 2:56, Box 2, Folder 59 [39153019697715])
  - C - Can, 1911-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:60 (Box 2, Folder 60 [39153019697723], Box-folder 2:60)
  - C. Bensinger Company, 1902-1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:61 (Box-folder 2:61, Box 2, Folder 61 [39153019697731])
  - C. Bischoff and Co., 1906-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:62 (Box 2, Folder 62 [39153019697749], Box-folder 2:62)
  - Cadwell, L. E., 1911-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:63 (Box-folder 2:63, Box 2, Folder 63 [39153019697756])
  - Caldwell, Brown, 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:64 (Box 2, Folder 64 [39153019697764], Box-folder 2:64)
  - California Agricultural Experiment Station, 1903-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:65 (Box 2, Folder 65 [39153019697772], Box-folder 2:65)
  - Camp, W. H., 1907-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:66 (Box 2, Folder 66 [39153019697780], Box-folder 2:66)
  - Campbell, Glenn H., 1918-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:67 (Box-folder 2:67, Box 2, Folder 67 [39153019697798])
  - Canada, 1900-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:68 (Box 2, Folder 68 [39153019697806], Box-folder 2:68)
  - Canadian Pheasantry, 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:69 (Box-folder 2:69, Box 2, Folder 69 [39153019697814])
  - Canfield, Edward T., 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:70 (Box 2, Folder 70 [39153019697822], Box-folder 2:70)
  - Cap - Cav, 1903-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:71 (Box 2, Folder 71 [39153019697830], Box-folder 2:71)
  - Capen, Charles A., 1904-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:72 (Box-folder 2:72, Box 2, Folder 72 [39153019697848])
  - Carbolineum Wood Preserving Company, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:73 (Box 2, Folder 73 [39153019697855], Box-folder 2:73)
  - Card, Leslie E., 1914-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:74 (Box 2, Folder 74 [39153019697863], Box-folder 2:74)
  - Card, W. H., 1910-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:75 (Box 2, Folder 75 [39153019697871], Box-folder 2:75)
  - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1907-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:76 (Box-folder 2:76, Box 2, Folder 76 [39153019697889])
    Carnegie Institution of Washington
  - Carter, Edward W., 1914-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:77 (Box 2, Folder 77 [39153019697897], Box-folder 2:77)
  - Case, Lockwood & Brainard Co., 1905-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:78 (Box-folder 2:78, Box 2, Folder 78 [39153019697905])
    Case, Lockwood & Brainard Co.
  - Case, Horace, 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:79 (Box-folder 2:79, Box 2, Folder 79 [39153019697913])
  - Case, Rosa C., 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:80 (Box-folder 2:80, Box 2, Folder 80 [39153019697921])
  - Cavanaugh, A. M., 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:81 (Box-folder 2:81, Box 2, Folder 81 [39153019697939])
  - Ce - Chap, 1902-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:82 (Box 2, Folder 82 [39153019697947], Box-folder 2:82)
  - Central Scientific Company, 1913-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:83 (Box-folder 2:83, Box 2, Folder 83 [39153019697954])
  - Chamberlain, L. P., 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:84 (Box-folder 2:84, Box 2, Folder 84 [39153019697962])
  - Chamberlin, Herbert B., 1911-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:85 (Box-folder 2:85, Box 2, Folder 85 [39153019697970])
  - Chandler, George B., 1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:86 (Box 2, Folder 86 [39153019697988], Box-folder 2:86)
  - Charles F. Hubbs Co., 1906-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:87 (Box 2, Folder 87 [39153019697996], Box-folder 2:87)
  - Chas - Chr, 1903-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:88 (Box-folder 2:88, Box 2, Folder 88 [39153019698002])
  - Cheney, Mark, 1911-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:89 (Box 2, Folder 89 [39153019698010], Box-folder 2:89)
  - Cheese, 1906-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:90 (Box-folder 2:90, Box 2, Folder 90 [39153019698028])
  - Chester, M. E., 1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:91 (Box 2, Folder 91 [39153019698036], Box-folder 2:91)
  - Chicago Flexible Shaft Company, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:92 (Box 2, Folder 92 [39153019698044], Box-folder 2:92)
  - Chicago House Wrecking Co., 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:93 (Box 2, Folder 93 [39153019698051], Box-folder 2:93)
  - Child, Chauncey S., 1908-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:94 (Box 2, Folder 94 [39153019698069], Box-folder 2:94)
  - Chile, 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:95 (Box-folder 2:95, Box 2, Folder 95 [39153019698077])
  - Chill - Ci, 1912-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:96 (Box-folder 2:96, Box 2, Folder 96 [39153019698085])
  - China, 1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:97 (Box-folder 2:97, Box 2, Folder 97 [39153019698093])
  - Christian Becker, 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:98 (Box 2, Folder 98 [39153019698101], Box-folder 2:98)
  - Cl - Clarke, J., 1912-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:99 (Box-folder 2:98, Box 2, Folder 98 [39153019698119])
  - Clapp, Raymond K., 1919-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:100 (Box-folder 2:100, Box 2, Folder 100 [39153019698127])
  - Clark, A. B., 1907-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:101 (Box-folder 2:101, Box 2, Folder 101 [39153019698135])
  - Clark, A. L., 1910-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:102 (Box-folder 2:102, Box 2, Folder 102 [39153019698143])
  - Clark, H. E., 1905-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:103 (Box-folder 2:103, Box 2, Folder 103 [39153019698150])
  - Clark, John W., 1909-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:104 (Box-folder 2:104, Box 2, Folder 104 [39153019698168])
  - Clark, L. - Clayton, 1908-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:105 (Box-folder 2:105, Box 2, Folder 105 [39153019698176])
  - Clay, Robinson Company, 1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:106 (Box 2, Folder 106 [39153019698184], Box-folder 2:106)
  - Clem - Clu, 1908-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:107 (Box-folder 2:107, Box 2, Folder 107 [39153019698192])
  - Clemson College, 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:108 (Box-folder 2:108, Box 2, Folder 108 [39153019698200])
    Clemson Agricultural College of South Carolina
  - Clinton L. A., 1902-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box2:109 (Box-folder 2:109, Box 2, Folder 109 [39153019698218])
  - Coa - Coi, 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:1 (Box-folder 3:1, Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Cobb, Albert W., 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:2 (Box 3, Folder 2, Box-folder 3:2)
  - Coc - Mortimer Company, 1905-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:3 (Box-folder 3:3, Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Codman and Shurtleff Inc., 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:4 (Box 3, Folder 4, Box-folder 3:4)
  - Col, 1909-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:5 (Box 3, Folder 5, Box-folder 3:5)
  - Colchester Jewish Farmers Association, 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:6 (Box 3, Folder 6, Box-folder 3:6)
  - Colorado Experiment Station, Colorado State University, 1906-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:7 (Box-folder 3:7, Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Columbia University, 1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:9 (Box-folder 3:9, Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Columbia Planter Company, 1913-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:8 (Box 3, Folder 8, Box-folder 3:8)
  - Com - Conl, 1909-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:10 (Box 3, Folder 10, Box-folder 3:10)
  - Comptometer, 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:11 (Box-folder 3:11, Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Comstock, Ferre and Company, 1918-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:12 (Box 3, Folder 12, Box-folder 3:12)
  - Conant, Ernest L., 1909-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:13 (Box 3, Folder 13, Box-folder 3:13)
  - Conley Foil Company, 1905-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:14 (Box 3, Folder 14, Box-folder 3:14)
  - Conn, H.W., 1894-1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:15 (Box-folder 3:15, Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Connecticut, 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:16 (Box 3, Folder 16, Box-folder 3:16)
  - Cac, 1915-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:17 (Box-folder 3:17, Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Connecticut Agricultural Experiment Station, 1901-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:18 (Box-folder 3:18, Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Connecticut Fairs, 1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:19 (Box 3, Folder 19, Box-folder 3:19)
  - Connecticut Instititute for the Blind, 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:20 (Box-folder 3:20, Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Connecticut Reformatory, 1916; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:21 (Box-folder 3:21, Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Connecticut Board of Agriculture, 1896-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:22 (Box 3, Folder 22, Box-folder 3:22)
  - Connecticut Commission on Domestic Animals, 1909-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:23 (Box-folder 3:23, Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Connecticut Commision of Fisheries and Game, 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:24 (Box 3, Folder 24, Box-folder 3:24)
  - Connecticut State Comptroller, 1900-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:25 (Box 3, Folder 25, Box-folder 3:25)
  - Connecticut Dairy and Food Commission, 1896-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:26 (Box 3, Folder 26, Box-folder 3:26)
  - Connecticut Dairymen's Association, 1896-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:27 (Box 3, Folder 27, Box-folder 3:27)
  - Connecticut Department of Education, 1918-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:28 (Box 3, Folder 28, Box-folder 3:28)
  - Connecticut Department of Health, 1918-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:29 (Box 3, Folder 29, Box-folder 3:29)
  - Conecticut Food Supply Committee, 1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:30 (Box-folder 3:30, Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Connecticut, Governor, 1896-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:31 (Box 3, Folder 31, Box-folder 3:31)
  - Connecticut Hospital for the Insane, 1902-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:32 (Box 3, Folder 32, Box-folder 3:32)
  - Connecticut Plant Breeder's Association, 1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:33 (Box 3, Folder 33, Box-folder 3:33)
  - Connecticut Pomological Society, 1906-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:34 (Box 3, Folder 34, Box-folder 3:34)
  - Connecticut Poultry Association, 1908-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:35 (Box 3, Folder 35, Box-folder 3:35)
  - Connecticut Secretary of State, 1896-1900; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:36 (Box 3, Folder 36, Box-folder 3:36)
  - Connecticut State Council of Defense, 1917-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:37 (Box-folder 3:37, Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Connecticut State Fair, 1908-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:38 (Box-folder 3:38, Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Connecticut State Farm for Women, 1918-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:39 (Box-folder 3:39, Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Connecticut State Fish and Game Commission, 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:40 (Box-folder 3:40, Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Connecticut State Grange, 1899-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:41 (Box-folder 3:41, Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Connecticut State Highway Commission, 1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:42 (Box 3, Folder 42, Box-folder 3:42)
  - Connecticut State Library, 1903-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:43 (Box-folder 3:43, Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Connecticut State Ornithologist, 1910-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:44 (Box-folder 3:44, Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Connecticut State Police, 1914-1916; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:45 (Box-folder 3:45, Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Connecticut State Prison, 1896-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:46 (Box-folder 3:46, Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Connel - Cooper, 1908-1916; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:47 (Box-folder 3:47, Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Cook, A.J., 1908-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:48 (Box-folder 3:48, Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Cook, Allen B., 1904-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:49 (Box-folder 3:49, Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Cook, Clarence P., 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:50 (Box 3, Folder 50, Box-folder 3:50)
  - Cook, Harry B., 1908-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:51 (Box-folder 3:51, Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Cop - Cost, 1911-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:52 (Box-folder 3:52, Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Cornell Cooperative Society, 1906-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:53 (Box-folder 3:53, Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Cornell Incubator Manufacturing Company, 1904-1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:54 (Box-folder 3:54, Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Cornell University, 1903-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:55 (Box 3, Folder 55, Box-folder 3:55)
  - Cou - Coyn, 1907-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:55.5 (Box-folder 3:55.5, Box 3, Folder 55.5)
  - Country Gentleman, 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:56 (Box 3, Folder 56, Box-folder 3:56)
  - Coventry Grange, 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:57 (Box 3, Folder 57, Box-folder 3:57)
  - Cox, Charles M., 1910-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:58 (Box 3, Folder 58, Box-folder 3:58)
  - Cra, 1913-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:59 (Box-folder 3:59, Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Crawford, H.B., 1911-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:60 (Box 3, Folder 60, Box-folder 3:60)
  - Cre - Cru, 1909-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:61 (Box-folder 3:61, Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Creamery Package Manufacturing Company, 1905-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:62 (Box 3, Folder 62, Box-folder 3:62)
  - Cromwell Creamery Association, 1894; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:63 (Box-folder 3:63, Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Cross, H.W., 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:64 (Box 3, Folder 64, Box-folder 3:64)
  - Cs - Cy, 1918-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:65 (Box 3, Folder 65, Box-folder 3:65)
  - Cuba, 1905-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:66 (Box 3, Folder 66, Box-folder 3:66)
  - Currie, James V., 1911-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:67 (Box-folder 3:67, Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Cutaway Harrow Company, 1907-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:68 (Box 3, Folder 68, Box-folder 3:68)
  - Cyphus Inoculator Company, 1903-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:69 (Box-folder 3:69, Box 3, Folder 69)
  - D - Dave, 1904-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:70 (Box-folder 3:70, Box 3, Folder 70)
  - D. Appleton and Company, 1904; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:71 (Box 3, Folder 71, Box-folder 3:71)
  - D.H. Burrell and Company, 1905-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:72 (Box-folder 3:72, Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Daniels Brothers (Millbrook Farm), 1903-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:73 (Box 3, Folder 73, Box-folder 3:73)
  - Darling and Company, 1905-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:74 (Box-folder 3:74, Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Davis, 1908-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:75 (Box-folder 3:75, Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Davis, Charles R., 1907-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:76 (Box-folder 3:76, Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Davis, G. Warren, 1909-1916; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:77 (Box 3, Folder 77, Box-folder 3:77)
  - Davis, Irving G., 1915-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:78 (Box-folder 3:78, Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Davison - Denk, 1903-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:79 (Box-folder 3:79, Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Davol Rubber Company, 1898-1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:80 (Box-folder 3:80, Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Dean, George Hamilton, 1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:81 (Box 3, Folder 81, Box-folder 3:81)
  - Deardon, Greenwood, 1905-1909; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:82 (Box-folder 3:82, Box 3, Folder 82)
  - DeBerard, Arthur J., 1904-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:83 (Box-folder 3:83, Box 3, Folder 83)
  - De Laval Dairy Supply Company, 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:84 (Box-folder 3:84, Box 3, Folder 84)
  - De Laval Separator Company, 1905-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:85 (Box-folder 3:85, Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Delaware Agricultural Experience Station, 1903-1915; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:86 (Box 3, Folder 86, Box-folder 3:86)
  - Deming, Grove, 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:87 (Box-folder 3:87, Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Deming, William C., 1912-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:88 (Box 3, Folder 88, Box-folder 3:88)
  - Denn - Dex, 1909-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:89 (Box 3, Folder 89, Box-folder 3:89)
  - Densmore Typewriter Company, 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:90 (Box 3, Folder 90, Box-folder 3:90)
  - Deyo, John M., 1911-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:91 (Box-folder 3:91, Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Dibble - Ditt, 1904-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:92 (Box 3, Folder 92, Box-folder 3:92)
  - Dibble Seed Company, 1914-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:93 (Box-folder 3:93, Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Dimoc, G. A., 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:94 (Box 3, Folder 94, Box-folder 3:94)
  - Divine, George H. M., 1909-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:95 (Box-folder 3:95, Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Doa - Doy, 1909-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:96 (Box 3, Folder 96, Box-folder 3:96)
  - Doherty, George J., 1909-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:97 (Box 3, Folder 97, Box-folder 3:97)
  - Dominick, George F., Jr., 1908-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:98 (Box 3, Folder 98, Box-folder 3:98)
  - Dorrance, Henry, 1905-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:99 (Box-folder 3:99, Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Dow Chemical Co., 1906-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:100 (Box 3, Folder 100, Box-folder 3:100)
  - Downs, Charles A. (Brooklyn Grange), 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:101 (Box-folder 3:101, Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Draper Manufacturing Company, 1904-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:102 (Box-folder 3:102, Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Dre - Dz, 1910-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:103 (Box 3, Folder 103, Box-folder 3:103)
  - Dann, E.R., 1905-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:104 (Box-folder 3:104, Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Dunning, Stewart N., 1908-1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box3:105 (Box 3, Folder 105, Box-folder 3:105)
  - E. - Edwards, 1909-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:1 (Box 4, Folder 1, Box-folder 4:1)
  - E.A. Buck and Company, 1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:2 (Box-folder 4:2, Box 4, Folder 2)
  - E. B. Estes and Son, 1905-1907; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:3 (Box 4, Folder 3, Box-folder 4:3)
  - E. Bigelow Company, 1896-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:4 (Box 4, Folder 4, Box-folder 4:4)
  - E. Frank Coe Company, 1903-1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:5 (Box 4, Folder 5, Box-folder 4:5)
  - E. I. DuPont de Nemours Powder Co., 1910-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:6 (Box-folder 4:6, Box 4, Folder 6)
  - E. P. Dutton and Co., 1910-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:7 (Box 4, Folder 7, Box-folder 4:7)
  - E and R Laundry Company, 1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:8 (Box-folder 4:8, Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Eagle Lock Co., 1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:9 (Box 4, Folder 9, Box-folder 4:9)
  - Earp - Thomas Farmogerm Co., 1908-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:10 (Box-folder 4:10, Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Eastern Safe Company, 1902; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:11 (Box 4, Folder 11, Box-folder 4:11)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1908-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:12 (Box 4, Folder 12, Box-folder 4:12)
  - Eaton, Edwin Choate, 1911-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:13 (Box 4, Folder 13, Box-folder 4:13)
  - Edmond, H. D., 1906-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:14 (Box-folder 4:14, Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Edwards, A. S., 1904-1905; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:15 (Box 4, Folder 15, Box-folder 4:15)
  - Egg - Ely, 1907-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:16 (Box-folder 4:16, Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Egypt - Ministry of Public Instruction, School of Agriculture, 1898; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:17 (Box-folder 4:17, Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Eimer and Amend, 1898-1917; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:18 (Box-folder 4:18, Box 4, Folder 18)
  - (El Salvador) Brannon, P. P., 1903; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:19 (Box-folder 4:19, Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Eldridge, Albert G., 1910-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:20 (Box 4, Folder 20, Box-folder 4:20)
  - Elliot Addressing Machine Co., 1904-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:21 (Box-folder 4:21, Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Elliot, George S., 1908-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:22 (Box-folder 4:22, Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Ellis, Benjamin W., 1917-1918; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:23 (Box-folder 4:23, Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Ellsworth, J. Lewis (Massachusetts Board of Agriculture), 1907-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:24 (Box 4, Folder 24, Box-folder 4:24)
  - Elwell, John D, 1910-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:25 (Box-folder 4:25, Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Em - Eye, 1910-1914; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:26 (Box-folder 4:26, Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Esperanza Farm (Fanny Morris Smith), 1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:27 (Box-folder 4:27, Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Essex Fertilizer Company, 1918-1920; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:28 (Box 4, Folder 28, Box-folder 4:28)
  - Esten, W. M., 1898-1916; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:29 (Box-folder 4:29, Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Eugene Dietzgen Company, 1913-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:30 (Box-folder 4:30, Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Eureka Mower Company, 1903-1906; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:31 (Box-folder 4:31, Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Evars, W.W., 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:32 (Box 4, Folder 32, Box-folder 4:32)
  - Everett B. Clark Seed Co., 1910; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:33 (Box 4, Folder 33, Box-folder 4:33)
  - F - Fay, 1896-1913; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:34 (Box 4, Folder 34, Box-folder 4:34)
  - F.W. Bird and Son, 1905-1911; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:35 (Box-folder 4:35, Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Faber, Jacob, 1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:36 (Box 4, Folder 36, Box-folder 4:36)
  - Fagan, Joseph A., 1903-1908; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:37 (Box-folder 4:37, Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Fairbanks Company, 1902-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:38 (Box 4, Folder 38, Box-folder 4:38)
  - Fairbanks, Morse and Co., 1914-1919; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:39 (Box-folder 4:39, Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Fanton, I. C., 1909-1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:40 (Box 4, Folder 40, Box-folder 4:40)
  - Farmers National Congress, 1912; 1972.0001\SeriesI\Box4:41 (Box 4, Folder 41, Box-folder 4:41)